e3internet.com 2013-05-03

# Privacy Policy

We sometimes use cookies to track how people arrive at GlobusDomains, your shopping cart contents and other details of site usage. This data is all stored in one single tiny cookie, and contains nothing that personally identifies you as an individual in any way.

Furthermore, we only record even this general and non-specific information if you actively choose to contact us through the site.

The only time we ever record any personal information is if you yourself openly choose to give it to us by contacting us, signing up to one of our newsletters or ordering goods or services through GlobusDomains. These details would only be the ones supplied such as your name, telephone number, billing address and/or email address.

## How This Information is Used

We may use the information you provide about yourself including your job function/title and company name to fulfill your requests for our products and services, to respond to your inquiries about services, newsletters, GlobusDomains events and any other services or products of GlobusDomains that we believe may be of interest to you.

We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, to notify you when your services with GlobusDomains are about to expire, to fulfill a request or order by you for our services, to email you important information relating to these services or contact you about your account with us.

We also use non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also use the information to aggregate and analyze site usage as well as offer products, programs and services of GlobusDomains.

Employees and contractors of GlobusDomains who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this privacy notice by not using this information other than to carry out the services they are performing for GlobusDomains.

In the case of secure online transactions, Credit Card numbers are not stored on our servers, only passed securely to our payment provider. If you choose to keep your credit card on file with us, then your details are strongly encrypted in our database.

Occasionally, GlobusDomains will send you offers, promotions and deals from GlobusDomains. At GlobusDomains we never releases any e-mail address information or details given on this site to any 3rd party vendor or marketing agency. Promotional e-mails transmitted by GlobusDomains are identified as coming from GlobusDomains. Any e-mail you may receive from GlobusDomains will always provide you with an opportunity to opt out or block such uses.

We will never use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.

## The Absolute Policy

We _**never**_ reveal, share or sell any information about any of our customers. Your data will be kept secure at all times. This is an unequivocal policy for us.
